lastcall.com 2016-06-01

# Security & Privacy at Neiman Marcus Last Call

#### Introduction

This website ("website") is operated by The Neiman Marcus Group, Inc., which includes Neiman Marcus stores, Neiman Marcus Direct, Horchow, and Bergdorf Goodman ("Neiman Marcus" or "we" or "us"). This privacy policy only covers information collected at this website, and does not cover any information collected offline by Neiman Marcus (unless specifically stated). All Neiman Marcus websites, including NeimanMarcus.com, BergdorfGoodman.com, Horchow.com, and LastCall.com, are currently covered by this privacy policy.

#### Security

Personal information provided on the website and online credit card transactions are transmitted through a secure server using Secure Socket Layering (SSL) encryption technology. When the letters "http" in the URL change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL; also, your browser may give you a pop-up message that you're about to enter a secure area.

You may purchase online merchandise by calling toll-free [1.800.888.4757](tel:18008884757)—24 hours a day, seven days a week. One of our customer service associates will gladly take your order.

We are committed to handling your personal information with high standards of information security. We take appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative steps to maintain the security and accuracy of personally identifiable information we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as employing electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. Our website uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address, and credit card number. Our Customer Care center and stores also operate over a private, secure network. Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.

#### Privacy Policy

To help us achieve our goal of providing the highest quality products and services, we use information from our interactions with you and other customers, as well as from other parties. Because we respect your privacy, we have implemented procedures to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner.

We have posted this privacy policy in order to explain our information collection practices and the choices you have about the way information is collected and used.

As we continue to develop our website and take advantage of advances in technology to improve the services we offer, this privacy policy likely will change. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 12, 2012. 

#### The Information We Collect

Generally, you may browse the website without providing any personally identifiable information. However, we may ask you to provide personally identifiable information at various times and places on this website. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you may not be able to access all of this website or participate in all of its features.

We receive and store any personally identifiable information you enter on the website, whenever you shop with Last Call online, through our catalogs, or in our stores, or information you give us in any other way, such as by subscribing to our catalogs, email, or mobile messaging. For example, we may collect the following personally identifiable information: your name, address, telephone number, mobile telephone number, driver's license number, birth date, and email address. If you use a credit or debit card or pay by check, we will also include your account number.

When you register with us as an online customer, we may ask for additional information, such as your favorite designers.

If you use one of our services, or participate in one of our surveys, promotions, or sweepstakes, we may ask for additional information, such as your age, interests, or product preferences.

From your purchases and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use.

When you visit this website, our web server automatically collects anonymous information such as log data and IP addresses, and may collect general information concerning your location. We may use the automatically collected information for a number of purposes, such as improving our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions. 

When you visit one of our stores, if your mobile device accesses one of our wireless networks we may also automatically collect information about your geo-location based, in part, upon which wireless network has been accessed. When this happens we attempt to de-identify the information, which means that we remove or change (e.g., hash) certain pieces of information that might be used to link the data to you, or to your device. We will not attempt to re-identify geo-location information (i.e., link it to you or your device) unless you affirmatively give us permission to collect geo-location information about you. If you give us such permission, you can later decide to opt-out via the mobile app you used to opt-in. To disable geo-location on your mobile device, open your Settings app, and tap Privacy. Then, tap on Location Services. Scroll down until you see the "NM" app and tap on the toggle on the right hand side so that the toggle is no longer green.

Our mobile applications will not transmit geo-location information about you to us unless you give them permission to do so.

Some web browsers and devices permit you to broadcast a preference that you not be "tracked" online. At this time we do not modify your experience based upon whether such a signal is broadcast. 

The Information We Collect was last updated December 5, 2014.

#### How We Use the Information We Collect

We use the information we collect for various purposes, including: 

  * To complete your purchase transactions
  * To provide the services you request 
  * To send you our catalogs and other offerings by mail 
  * To identify your product and service preferences, so we can notify you of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you 
  * To notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased 
  * To improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall shopping experience 

#### Others With Whom We Share Your Information

The Neiman Marcus Group: All of the above information that we collect, as described above, may be shared among all Neiman Marcus entities, including Horchow and Bergdorf Goodman.

Service Providers: We also may disclose information to outside companies that help us bring you the products and services we offer. For example, we may work with an outside company to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist us in distributing emails; (c) assist us with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide us storage and analysis; (d) provide fraud prevention; and (e) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. We require that these outside companies agree to keep confidential all information we share with them and to use the information only to perform their obligations in our agreements with them.

Other Companies: We may provide information to carefully selected outside companies when we believe their products or services may be of interest to you.

Business Transitions: We may transfer or share a copy of personal information about you in the event that Neiman Marcus or one of its properties, affiliates, or subsidiaries goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our website prior to a change of ownership or control of your personal information, if your personal information will be used contrary to this policy. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with the ability of Neiman Marcus to transfer all or part of its business and/or assets to an affiliate or independent third party at any time, for any purpose, without any limitation whatsoever. Neiman Marcus specifically reserves the right to transfer or share a copy of personally identifiable information collected from its websites to the buyer of that portion of its business relating to that information.

Compliance with Law: We may provide access to information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website, to limit our legal liability, and to protect our rights or to protect the rights, property, or safety of visitors of this website or the public. 

Last Call partners with advertising companies to place our advertising on publisher websites on the Internet. These advertising companies collect anonymous information about your visits to our website. This technology involves the use of third party cookies which allow them to develop personalized advertising so that it directly relates to offers that may be of interest to you. To choose to opt out of this service we have with our third-party advertising partner, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed). We may also use Neiman Marcus cookies to provide similar enhanced online marketing to you based on your interests and preferences. To opt out of these enhanced online marketing ads, please [click here](http://dtmc.lastcall.com/adinfo/adchoices_fpc.html?cid=2426&cname=Last%20Call&cmagic=c65d7b&clogo=lastcall.png).

#### Your Choices Regarding Use of the Information We Collect

We provide you with a number of choices regarding our handling of your nonpublic personally identifiable information. 

Direct Mail or Telephone Marketing: If you shop at the Neiman Marcus or Bergdorf Goodman stores and wish to be removed from the list of customers that receive direct mail or telemarketing calls, please either: 

  * Write to: Neiman Marcus Customer Care at P.O. Box 650589, Dallas, Texas, 75265-0589
  * or call toll-free [1.800.456.5488](tel:18004565488)

If you choose to write to us, please include your name, address, and credit card account number (if you have one), and state one of the following: 

  * "NO MAIL OFFERS" (if you don't want to receive offers by mail);
  * "NO PHONE OFFERS" (if you don't want to receive offers by phone); or
  * "NO PHONE OR MAIL OFFERS" (if you don't want to receive either).

Because customer lists often are prepared well in advance of an offering (sometimes a few months before the offer is made), you may continue to receive some offers after you send us a request not to use your information for specified marketing purposes. We appreciate your patience and understanding in giving us time to carry out your request. 

Please note that we do not offer an opt out from sharing nonpublic personally identifiable information about you among Neiman Marcus Group entities. 

#### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Neiman Marcus Customer Care, P.O.Box 650589, Dallas, Texas 75265-0589. Please allow 30 days for a response. 

#### Cookies, Web Beacons, and How We Use Them

A "cookie" is a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer or mobile device [hard drive]. It allows us to recognize your computer (but not specifically who is using it) upon entering our site by associating the identification numbers in the cookie with other customer information you have provided us. That customer information is stored on our secured database. A "web beacon" or "pixel tag" or "clear gif" is typically a one-pixel image, used to pass information from your computer or a mobile device to a website.

We use cookies and web beacons to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to the website as well as to identify the pages you click on during your visit to our site and the name of the website you visited immediately before clicking to LastCall.com. We use this information to improve our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions. You can, of course, disable cookies and web beacons on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of our website will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. We may also use web beacons, and other technologies, to help track whether our communications are reaching you, to measure their effectiveness, or to collect certain non-personal information about your computer, device, or browser in order to allow us to better design future communications to you.

We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and web beacons and collect information on our behalf or provide services such as credit card processing, shipping, promotional services, or data management. We call them our Customer Care Partners. These third parties are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our other Customer Care Partners. 

Cookies, Web Beacons, and How We Use Them was last updated on March 7, 2013.

#### Children's Privacy

Protecting children's privacy is important to us. Our website is a general audience site. We do not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is targeted to attract anyone under 13. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without their parent's consent.

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the web. 

#### Links to Other Sites

While visiting LastCall.com, you may link to websites operated by our business partners or other third parties. This does not mean that we endorse these websites. We do not make any representations or warranties about any website you may access through this website. They are independent from us, and we have no control over, or responsibility for, their information or activities.

In addition, our privacy practices may differ from those of these other sites. If you provide personal information at one of those sites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that site, not the Neiman Marcus Privacy Policy. Make sure you understand any website's privacy policies before providing personal information.

#### Online Account Registration

To make online shopping faster and easier, you may register with LastCall.com. As a registered customer, you only have to enter your shipping addresses and billing information once; they will be securely stored with us for your future use. Using your name and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete, or change information.

If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to LOG OUT at the conclusion of your session. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer.

#### Emails

You will receive promotional emails from us only if you have asked to receive them. If you do not want to receive email from Neiman Marcus or its affiliates you can click on the "Manage Your Email Preferences" link at the bottom of any email communication sent by us. Choose "Unsubscribe" at the bottom of the page that opens. Please allow us 3 business days from when the request was received to complete the removal, as some of our promotions may already have been in process before you submitted your request.

#### Mobile Messaging

If you've signed up for mobile messaging (e.g., SMS and MMS) offers but later decide you no longer wish to receive them, simply follow the opt-out instructions included in the mobile message or [click here.](http://bit.ly/tcNMLC)

#### Acceptance

By using this website, you accept the policies set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

#### Any questions?

We'll be happy to provide additional information or answer any questions. Please: 

**Call toll-free** [1.800.456.5488](tel:18004565488)

**Write:**

  * Customer Care
  * P.O. Box 650589
  * Dallas, TX 75265-0589
